<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<gantrytips>
	
	<tip label="Top Positions" id="top"><![CDATA[Use the layout slider to select the desired column distribution (width) used for the <strong>Top Positions.</strong> The active value will be highlighted in blue and underlined. The <strong>Force Positionss</strong> attribute causes all the Top positions to be displayed. If there is no module published in a position, then a blank space is left. The position count controls the number of forced positions.]]></tip>

	<tip label="Navigation Positions" id="navigation"><![CDATA[Use the layout slider to select the desired column distribution (width) used for the <strong>Navigation Positions.</strong> The active value will be highlighted in blue and underlined. The <strong>Force Positionss</strong> attribute causes all the Navigation positions to be displayed. If there is no module published in a position, then a blank space is left. The position count controls the number of forced positions.]]></tip>
	
	<tip label="Header Positions" id="header"><![CDATA[Use the layout slider to select the desired column distribution (width) used for the <strong>Header Positions.</strong> The active value will be highlighted in blue and underlined. The <strong>Force Positionss</strong> attribute causes all the Header positions to be displayed. If there is no module published in a position, then a blank space is left. The position count controls the number of forced positions.]]></tip>
	
	<tip label="Showcase Positions" id="showcase"><![CDATA[Use the layout slider to select the desired column distribution (width) used for the <strong>Showcase Positions.</strong> The active value will be highlighted in blue and underlined. The <strong>Force Positionss</strong> attribute causes all the Showcase positions to be displayed. If there is no module published in a position, then a blank space is left. The position count controls the number of forced positions.]]></tip>
	
	<tip label="Feature Positions" id="feature"><![CDATA[Use the layout slider to select the desired column distribution (width) used for the <strong>Feature Positions.</strong> The active value will be highlighted in blue and underlined. The <strong>Force Positionss</strong> attribute causes all the Feature positions to be displayed. If there is no module published in a position, then a blank space is left. The position count controls the number of forced positions.]]></tip>
	
	<tip label="Utility Positions" id="utility"><![CDATA[Use the layout slider to select the desired column distribution (width) used for the <strong>Utility Positions.</strong> The active value will be highlighted in blue and underlined. The <strong>Force Positionss</strong> attribute causes all the Utility positions to be displayed. If there is no module published in a position, then a blank space is left. The position count controls the number of forced positions.]]></tip>
	
	<tip label="MainTop Positions" id="maintop"><![CDATA[Use the layout slider to select the desired column distribution (width) used for the <strong>MainTop Positions.</strong> The active value will be highlighted in blue and underlined. The <strong>Force Positionss</strong> attribute causes all the MainTop positions to be displayed. If there is no module published in a position, then a blank space is left. The position count controls the number of forced positions.]]></tip>
	
	<tip label="MainBody Positions" id="mainbodyPositions"><![CDATA[Use the layout slider to select the desired column distribution (width) used for the <strong>MainBody Positions.</strong> The active value will be highlighted in blue and underlined. You can also use the slider to decide on which side of the MainBody you would like to display the <strong>Sidebar Positionss.</strong>]]></tip>

	<tip label="MainBottom Positions" id="mainbottom"><![CDATA[Use the layout slider to select the desired column distribution (width) used for the <strong>MainBottom Positions.</strong> The active value will be highlighted in blue and underlined. The <strong>Force Positionss</strong> attribute causes all the MainBottom positions to be displayed. If there is no module published in a position, then a blank space is left. The position count controls the number of forced positions.]]></tip>

	<tip label="Extension Positions" id="bottom"><![CDATA[Use the layout slider to select the desired column distribution (width) used for the <strong>Extension Positions.</strong> The active value will be highlighted in blue and underlined. The <strong>Force Positionss</strong> attribute causes all the Extension positions to be displayed. If there is no module published in a position, then a blank space is left. The position count controls the number of forced positions.]]></tip>

	<tip label="Bottom Positions" id="bottom"><![CDATA[Use the layout slider to select the desired column distribution (width) used for the <strong>Bottom Positions.</strong> The active value will be highlighted in blue and underlined. The <strong>Force Positionss</strong> attribute causes all the Bottom positions to be displayed. If there is no module published in a position, then a blank space is left. The position count controls the number of forced positions.]]></tip>

	<tip label="Footer Positions" id="footer"><![CDATA[Use the layout slider to select the desired column distribution (width) used for the <strong>Footer Positions.</strong> The active value will be highlighted in blue and underlined. The <strong>Force Positionss</strong> attribute causes all the Footer positions to be displayed. If there is no module published in a position, then a blank space is left. The position count controls the number of forced positions.]]></tip>
	
	<tip label="Copyright Positions" id="copyright"><![CDATA[Use the layout slider to select the desired column distribution (width) used for the <strong>Copyright Positions.</strong> The active value will be highlighted in blue and underlined. The <strong>Force Positionss</strong> attribute causes all the Footer positions to be displayed. If there is no module published in a position, then a blank space is left. The position count controls the number of forced positions.]]></tip>

</gantrytips>